NICOLE Y WALTON

545 Southport Dr, Dallas TX 75232 Home: 214-809-7254 CREATIVENICOLE1981@GMAIL.COM

Professional Summary

CERTIFIED NURSING ASSISTANT with current TEXAS Department of Health Certification. 10 years experience with physically disabled client. Monitored vital signs, assisted with feeding, bathing/grooming, positioning and range of motion exercises. Looking for a position in hospice or a hospital/clinical.I also work with dialysis patients preparing needle sticks to dialyzed them.

Licenses

CPR certified through American Heart Association Certified Nursing Assistant #8595510

Professional Experience

DALLAS TRANSITIONAL CENTER

September 2014 to March 2017

GUARD (CLIENT MONITOR)

Fort Worth, TX

THIS IS A HALF WAY UNITED FOR INMATES WHO DONT HAVE HOME PLANS WHEN THEY ARE RELEASED FROM PRISON. THIS IS A STATE JOB. Devised short and long-range action plans to address a wide variety of municipal needs. Secured funding for emergency, housing rehabilitation and transportation services in the community. Directed city renovations that benefited over 200 residents.

Kindred Hospita April 2018 to Current

CNA

Arlington, TX

- Provided quality nursing care in accordance with resident care policies and procedures.
- Obtained vitals for a floor of 25 patients per shift.
- Took and recorded patients' temperature, pulse and blood pressure.
- Provided caring companionship to elderly and developmentally disabled patients.

Fresenius Kidne April 2017 to April 2018

PCT

Dallas, TX

- Interviewed patients to obtain medical information and measure their vital signs, weight and height.
- Completed daily rounds of the nursing department to verify that all nursing service personnel were performing their work assignments in accordance with acceptable nursing standards.
- Utilized strong assessment skills to determine necessary patient care.
- Took and recorded patients' temperature, pulse and blood pressure.
- Evaluated patient care needs, prioritized treatment and maintained patient flow.

Education and Training

BELFORD HIGH SCHOOL High School Diploma: DIPLOMA 1999

HUMBLE, TX, HARRIS